Tufts Magazine UP052
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Magazine
1994 -- 2016
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Alumni Relations
UP052
1.5 Linear Feet
15 Digital Object(s)
152.2 Megabytes
This collection contains the alumni magazine of Tufts University. Tufts Magazine contains news about the university for alumni. It includes feature articles as well as news from alumni organizations and individuals.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the alumni magazine of Tufts University. Tufts Magazine contains news about the university for alumni. It includes feature articles as well as news from alumni organizations and individuals. The Tuftonia replaced the Criterion as the official alumni magazine in 1994. The Tuftonia changed its name to Tufts Magazine beginning in Fall 2000.
Related Materials
UP053, Tufts Criterion, DCA
UP003, Tufts Topics, DCA
UP004, Tufts Alumni Review, DCA
UP065, Tufts Review, DCA
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically in one series, Tufts Magazine.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
- Tufts Magazine, 1994 -- 2020; UP052.001; 1.5 Linear Feet; 15 Digital Object(s); 152.2 Megabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the alumni magazine of Tufts University. Tufts Magazine contains news about the university for alumni. It includes feature articles as well as news from alumni organizations and individuals. The Tuftonia replaced the Criterion as the official alumni magazine in 1994. The Tuftonian changed its name to Tufts Magazine beginning in Fall 2000.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tuftonia, Winter, 1994; UP052.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    [Alumni relations] Up front: a letter from Ron Brinn; Adams, Benjamin C. (A88) Class notes; married Jennifer Goldsmith. p. 51.; Adams, Suzanne (Marcoux) (J67). Class notes. p. 45; Addleton, Jonathan (F82). Class notes. p. 48. [Admissions 1994] Apply yourself by disk. [Admissions 1994] Letter of response; aid should be help, not handout. Babak Alizadeh (A82, G85) and Elizabeth Alizadeh (Bergl) (J84) Class notes; announces birth of son. Susan L. Allen (J87) Class notes; married Dr. Andrew John Nelson. [Alumni 1994] Letter of response; aid should be help, not handout, p. 2. Keep class notes, p. 2. Jumbo's back, p. 5. Opening the door through admissions, p. 5. Talloires program for alums, p. 9. Jones, Bob; a Tufts ringleader, p.11. Recent activities of Tufts Alliance Network, p. 38-39. [Alumni 1994] Tales from Abroad, p. 29-31. Shapiro, Neal; an interview, p. 32, 33. Siegal, Adam; feeling "zooish" in Boston, p. 56.
  - Tuftonia, Spring, 1994; UP052.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Fall, 1994 -- 1995; UP052.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    [Amalgamate] Something to sing about: The mates celebrate their tenth; [Alumni council] Jumbo fest; [Alumni 1994-95] Alumni Weekend '94, p. 27. [Alumni 1994-95] Learning doesn't end at graduations, p. 24, 53.
  - Tuftonia, Winter, 1995; UP052.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    Dr. Sara J. Albertelli (E90), (M94) and Edward Lee ('91) Married on June 12. Dr. Hollis L. Albright ('27) Died. Edith Alexander (faculty) In Memoriam. Myron Allukian ('60) President of the American Board of Dental Public Health. Amy Almeida (88) Graduation Announcement, p.40.
  - Tuftonia, Spring, 1995; UP052.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Summer, 1995; UP052.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    Ackerman, Raymond ('46) In memoriam. p. 45.; Addleton, Jonathan (F89) Baby announcement, November 2, 1994. Career Update. p. 39.; [Adzigian, Mark '88] Marriage announcement: September 4, 1994. p. 41. [Alaimo, Melissa '85] Baby announcement: March 8, 1994, 2 children. Virgil Alello ('63) Career information. Kelley Alessi (90) Career update. [Alfonso, Marita] (92) Career update.
  - Tuftonia, Fall, 1995; UP052.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Winter, 1996; UP052.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Spring, 1996; UP052.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Summer, 1996; UP052.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Fall, 1996 -- 1997; UP052.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Winter, 1997; UP052.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Spring, 1997; UP052.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Summer, 1996 -- 1997; UP052.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Fall, 1997; UP052.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Winter, 1997 -- 1998; UP052.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Spring, 1998; UP052.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Summer, 1998; UP052.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Fall, 1998 -- 1999; UP052.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Winter, 1999; UP052.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Spring, 1998 -- 1999; UP052.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Summer, 1999; UP052.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Fall, 1999 -- 2000; UP052.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Winter, 1999 -- 2000; UP052.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Spring, 1999 -- 2000; UP052.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Tuftonia, Summer, 1999 -- 2000; UP052.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2000; UP052.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2001; UP052.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2001; UP052.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2001; UP052.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2001; UP052.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2002; UP052.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2002; UP052.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
    This item was used in the spring 2012 reunion exhibit.
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2002; UP052.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2002; UP052.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2002; UP052.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room.
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2003; UP052.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2003; UP052.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2003; UP052.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2003; UP052.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2004; UP052.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2004; UP052.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2004; UP052.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2004; UP052.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2005; UP052.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2005; UP052.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2005; UP052.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2005; UP052.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2006; UP052.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2006; UP052.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2006; UP052.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Tutfs Magazine, Fall, 2006; UP052.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
    2nd copy in bound volume in reading room
    Volume, issue
    14, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2007; UP052.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    14, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2007; UP052.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
    XIV, 3
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2007; UP052.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
    XIV, 4
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2007; UP052.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
    XV, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2008; UP052.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
    XV, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2008; UP052.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
    XV, 3
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2008; UP052.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
    XV, 4
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2009; UP052.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
    XVI, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2009; UP052.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
    (mislabeled as Vol XVII)
    XVI, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2009; UP052.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
    XVII, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2010; UP052.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
    XVII, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2010; UP052.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
    XVII, 3
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2010; UP052.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
    XVIII, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2011; UP052.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
    XVIII, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2011; UP052.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
    XVIII, 3
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2011; UP052.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
    XIX, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2012; UP052.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
    XIX, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2012; UP052.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
    XIX, 3
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2012; UP052.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
    XX, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2013; UP052.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
    XX, 3
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2013; UP052.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    XX, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2013; UP052.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
    XXI, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2014; UP052.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
    XXI, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2014; UP052.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
    XXI, 3
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2014; UP052.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
    22, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Winter, 2015; UP052.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
    22, 2
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2015; UP052.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
    23, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2016; UP052.001.003.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2018; UP052.001.003.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Volume, Number
    26, 1
  - Tufts Magazine, Summer, 2015; UP052.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2016; UP052.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2017; UP052.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall, 2017; UP052.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Tufts Magazine, Spring, 2018; UP052.001.00005; 1 Digital Object(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall 2019; UP052.000090 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tufts Magazine, Fall 2020; UP052.000089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    28, 1